A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Healthy Steps for Young Children Program, SG 2, Series 6 FA498
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Files, 1989-2005; 3
  - Beep Program - Boston - J. Palfrey Info, 1989, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 321)
  - Brain Development, 1995-2000 (Box 69, Folder 322)
  - Brain Development - Miscellaneous, 1996-2000 (Box 69, Folder 323)
  - Communication Strategy, 1994-1996 (Box 69, Folder 324)
  - Communication Strategy, 1994-1996 (Box 69, Folder 325)
  - Contact Binder, 1995-1996 (Box 70, Folder 326)
  - Consumer Assessments of Health Plans Study, 1996 Aug. (Box 70, Folder 327)
  - Co-Sponsors - AAP - Catch, 1995-1997 (Box 70, Folder 328)
  - Foundation Grants Guidelines, 1997-1998 (Box 70, Folder 329)
  - Alan Guttmacher Reports, 2000 April - May (Box 70, Folder 330)
  - Alan Guttmacher Reports, 2000 June-July (Box 71, Folder 331)
  - Alan Guttmacher Reports, 2000 August (Box 71, Folder 332)
  - Alan Guttmacher Reports, 2000 September-November (Box 71, Folder 333)
  - Home Visiting - Kay Johnson, 1999-2001 (Box 71, Folder 334)
  - Home Visiting - Kay Johnson, 1998-2001 (Box 71, Folder 335)
  - ICF Incorporated - Consulting Project - Mike Barth, 1994 Nov. (Box 71, Folder 336)
  - Insurer Survey, 2002 (Box 72, Folder 337)
  - Jane Knitzer - National Center for Children/Poverty, 1998-2000 (Box 72, Folder 338)
  - Legal Issues - 96180 Legal Issues, 1996-2000 (Box 72, Folder 339)
  - Legal Issues - White & Case, 1995-2000 (Box 72, Folder 340)
  - Legal Issues - Beansprout/BU Letter of Intent, 1999-2001 (Box 72, Folder 341)
  - Log - Pages 1-175, 2005 Aug. - Oct. (Box 72, Folder 342)
  - Log - Pages 176 - 227, 2005 Aug. - Oct. (Box 73, Folder 343)
  - Operations Manual for Affiliate Sites, 1997 June (Box 73, Folder 344)
  - Operations Manual for Evaluation Sites, 1997 February (Box 73, Folder 345)
  - Operations Manual for Evaluation Sites, 1997 February (Box 73, Folder 346)
  - Current Operations, 2001-2002 (Box 73, Folder 347)
  - Parenting - Carnegie Corporation, 1993-1996 (Box 73, Folder 348)
  - Parenting - Parent Education Programs, 1992-1994 (Box 74, Folder 349)
  - Parenting Survey Findings - Ramsey Associates, 1988-1994 (Box 74, Folder 350)
  - Parenting - Press Clippings, 1988-1994 (Box 74, Folder 351)
  - Parenting - Press Clippings, 1994-1995 (Box 74, Folder 352)
  - Parenting - Press Clippings, 1995 (Box 74, Folder 353)
  - Parenting - Press Clippings, 1996-1997 (Box 74, Folder 354)
  - Pediatrics, 1996-1998 (Box 75, Folder 355)
  - Pediatrics, 1997-1998 (Box 75, Folder 356)
  - The New Pediatrics for Families with Young Children, 1998 Nov. (Box 75, Folder 357)
  - Program Plans, 1997-1998 (Box 75, Folder 358)
  - Program Plans, 1997-1998 (Box 75, Folder 359)
  - Program Plans - Objectives and Website, 1997-1998 (Box 75, Folder 360)
  - Program Plans - Materials, 1998 September (Box 76, Folder 361)
  - Program Plans, 1998 (Box 76, Folder 362)
  - Program Plans, 1998-1999 (Box 76, Folder 363)
  - Program Plans, 1999 April-September (Box 76, Folder 364)
  - Program Plans, 1999-2000 (Box 76, Folder 365)
  - Program Plans, 2001 (Box 76, Folder 366)
  - Program Monitoring Committee Meeting 2002 July 9, 1999-2002 (Box 77, Folder 367)
  - Child Development & Pediatric Care - Program Plan Materials, 2001-2003 (Box 77, Folder 368)
  - Program for Child Development & Pediatric Care, 2002 May 30 (Box 77, Folder 369)
  - Final Program Plan - Notes/Discussion, 2003 (Box 77, Folder 370)
  - Program for Child Development and Preventive Care, 2003 October 16 (Box 78, Folder 371)
  - Program for Child Development and Preventive Care, 2003-2004 (Box 78, Folder 372)
  - Protocol, 1996 (Box 78, Folder 373)
  - Provider Measures - JHU, 1996 (Box 79, Folder 374)
  - Parent Measures - JHU, 1997-1999 (Box 79, Folder 375)
  - First Year Provider Instruments, 1998 January 21 (Box 79, Folder 376)
  - 15 Month Provider Instruments - JHU, 1998 February 27 (Box 79, Folder 377)
  - 15 Month Provider Instruments - JHU, 1998 February 27 (Box 79, Folder 378)
  - 30 Month Provider Instruments - JHU, 1999 Feb. 15 (Box 80, Folder 379)
  - Reimbursement Tool Kit, 2002 July 1 (Box 80, Folder 380)
  - Replication - Correspondence - 96180, 1996 (Box 80, Folder 381)
  - Replication, 1997-2000 (Box 80, Folder 382)
  - Replication, 2000-2001 (Box 80, Folder 383)
  - Specialist Lists, 1996 (Box 80, Folder 384)
  - Southern Regional Education Board - Legislative Report, 1994 (Box 80, Folder 385)
  - Boston University Technical Assistance - Conference Call Summaries, 1996-2000 (Box 81, Folder 386)
  - Boston University Technical Assistance, 1996-2000 (Box 81, Folder 387)
  - Technical Assistance to Local Initiatives - BU, JHU, & ICF, 1998 January-June (Box 81, Folder 388)
  - Technical Assistance to Local Initiatives - BU, JHU, & ICF, 1998 July-December (Box 81, Folder 389)
  - Technical Assistance to Local Initiatives - BU, JHU, & ICF, 1999 (Box 82, Folder 390)
  - Toby Levine Communications, Inc. - Responses to Drafts of Healthy Steps Manual, 1998 July 31, 2000 March 16 (Box 82, Folder 391)
  - Toby Levine Communications, Inc. - Responses to Drafts of Healthy Steps Manual, 1998 July 31, 2000 March 16 (Box 82, Folder 392)
  - Toby Levine Communications, Inc. - Responses to Drafts of Healthy Steps Manual, 1998 July 31, 2000 March 16 (Box 82, Folder 393)
  - Training - Year One Training Manual and Reader - Draft for Review - Toby Levine - Andrea, 1998 July 31 (Box 82, Folder 394)
  - Training - Year One Training Manual and Reader - Draft for Review - Toby Levine - KTM, 1998 July 31 (Box 83, Folder 395)
  - Training - Year One Training Manual and Reader - Draft for Review - Toby Levine - Kathleen Fitzgerald Rice, 1998 Jult 31 (Box 83, Folder 396)
  - Training - Putting Healthy Steps into Practice - HS Training Manual, 1996 October (Box 83, Folder 397)
  - Training - Putting Healthy Steps into Practice - HS Training Manual, 1996 October (Box 83, Folder 398)
  - Training - Boston University Training Material Year 2 - Board Meeting Nov. 1997, 1997-1998 (Box 84, Folder 399)
  - Training - Planner - Year III Training Institute - Growing Up - Year III and Beyond, 1999 May 14-16 (Box 84, Folder 400)
  - Training - Planner - Year III Training Institute - Growing Up - Year III and Beyond, 1999 May 14-16 (Box 84, Folder 401)
  - Training - Year III Training Institute - Sustainability, 1999 May 15-16 (Box 84, Folder 402)
  - Training - Year III Training Institute - Sustainability, 1999 May 15-16 (Box 84, Folder 403)
  - Sustainability, 1999-2001 (Box 84, Folder 404)
  - Staff Training, Implementation, and Materials - Phase Six - BSMU, 2000-2001 (Box 85, Folder 405)
  - Training/Curriculum Material - Staff Cv's, 1995 (Box 85, Folder 406)
  - Training - Curriculum - Faxes for Margo, 1995-1996 (Box 85, Folder 407)
  - KTY Meeting, 1995 July 10 (Box 85, Folder 408)
  - Training Material - Notes - KTY & BZ, 1995 (Box 85, Folder 409)
  - Training Institute Venus - Kansas City, 2003 (Box 85, Folder 410)
  - Kathryn Taaffe Young Files, 1
    - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 85, Folder 411)
    - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 85, Folder 412)
    - Correspondence, 1996 (Box 86, Folder 413)
    - Correspondence, 1996 (Box 86, Folder 414)
    - Correspondence, 1997 (Box 86, Folder 415)
    - Correspondence, 1997 (Box 87, Folder 416)
    - Correspondence, 1998 (Box 87, Folder 417)
    - Correspondence, 1999 January-March (Box 87, Folder 418)
    - Correspondence, 1999 April-June (Box 88, Folder 419)
    - Correspondence, 1999 July-September (Box 88, Folder 420)
    - Correspondence, 1999 October-December (Box 88, Folder 421)
    - Notes From Phone Calls - 96014, 1995 Jan. 23 (Box 88, Folder 422)
    - Boston University Meeting - Zuckerman, KTY, & MB, 1995 April 5 (Box 88, Folder 423)
    - Baby - Child Learning - Kit for Mothers & Fathers - Meeting, 1995 Sept. 28 (Box 88, Folder 424)
    - Parenting Materials Meeting, 1995 Sept. 28 (Box 88, Folder 425)
    - Boston University - Curriculum Themes 96014, 1995 October (Box 88, Folder 426)
    - Boston University - Administration 96014, 1995-1996 (Box 88, Folder 427)
    - Boston University - Correspondence 96014, 1995-1996 (Box 88, Folder 428)
    - Boston University - Proposal 96014, 1995-1996 (Box 88, Folder 429)
    - Boston University - Specialist 96650, 1995-1996 (Box 88, Folder 430)
    - Boston University - Phase 2, KTY Notes 96650, 1997 (Box 88, Folder 431)
    - Boston University - Phase 2, Budget, P&R, LOA, Proposal 96650, 1996-1998 (Box 88, Folder 432)
    - Boston University - Phase 2, Correspondence 96650, 1996-1998 (Box 88, Folder 433)
    - Boston University - July Training Institute 96650, 1996-1997 (Box 88, Folder 434)
    - ICF Inc. Affiliate Sites - Technical Assistance Plan 96957, 1997 Jan. 14 (Box 88, Folder 435)
    - KTM Child Health & Development Record, 1997-1998 (Box 88, Folder 436)
    - KTM Travel in D.C., 1999 March 7-9 (Box 89, Folder 437)
    - KTM Trrvel - Site Visit Allentown, 1999 Feb. (Box 89, Folder 438)
    - Local Funders Network Meeting - GIH Tempe, Arizona, 1999 Feb. 17 (Box 89, Folder 439)
    - May National Advisory Committee Meeting, 1999 (Box 89, Folder 440)
    - May 1999 National Advisory Committee Meeting, 1999 May (Box 89, Folder 441)
    - Meeting at the Intercontinental Hotel - Conference, 1999 May 25 (Box 89, Folder 442)
    - Policy Makers Multimedia - Committee Contact Lists, 1998-1999 (Box 89, Folder 443)
    - Preparation for Healthy Steps Evaluation Meeting, 1999 Feb. 22 (Box 89, Folder 444)
    - Workshop - The Science of Developmental Promotion and Early Childhood Intervention, 1999 June 24-25 (Box 89, Folder 445)
    - Zero To Three - Scientific Meeting, 1999 May 19-23 (Box 89, Folder 446)
    - Randi Gould Correspondence - Healthy Steps Manuscript, 1998 (Box 89, Folder 447)
    - ELS Correspondence 1 of 2, 2002-2005 (Box 89, Folder 448)
    - ELS Correspondence 2 of 2, 2002-2005 (Box 89, Folder 449)
  - Margaret E. Mahoney - Correspondence, Meeting and Planning Files, 1990s (Box 186, Folder 1189-1196)
  - Margaret E. Mahoney - Correspondence, Meeting and Planning Files, 1990s (Box 187, Folder 1197-1211)
  - Margaret E. Mahoney - Correspondence, Meeting and Planning Files, 1990s (Box 188, Folder 1212-1216)
  - Healthy Steps Program Video - General Audience, 1998 (Box 188, Folder 1217)
  - Maine Obesity Prevention Project Manual, 2005 (Box 188, Folder 1218)
  - Margaret E. Mahoney - Correspondence, Meeting and Planning Files, 2000s (Box 189, Folder 1219-1225)
  - Margaret E. Mahoney - Correspondence, Meeting and Planning Files, 2000s (Box 190, Folder 1226-1229)
- Grants, 1991-2006; 4
  - Adolescent Health Book - Author's Chapter - Cleo Caldwell, 1998 Oct. 8 (Box 90, Folder 450)
  - Adolescent Health Book - Author's Chapter - Sherry Glied/Dan Pines - Mental Health Chapter, 1998 (Box 90, Folder 451)
  - Adolescent Health Book - Author's Chapter - Liz Goodman - Socioeconomic Status Chapter, 1998 (Box 90, Folder 452)
  - Adolescent Health Book - Author's Chapter - Barbara Guthrie - Prospective Author, 1999 (Box 90, Folder 453)
  - Adolescent Health Book - Author's Chapter - Jon Klein - Access Chapter, 1998 (Box 90, Folder 454)
  - Adolescent Health Book - Author's Chapter - Diane Neumark - Steiner - Eating Disorders Chapter, 1998-1999 (Box 90, Folder 455)
  - Adolescent Health Book - Author's Chapter - Stacey Plichta/Larry Wissow - Violence/Abuse Chapter, 1998 (Box 90, Folder 456)
  - Adolescent Health Book - Author's Chapter - Marta Tienda - Hispanic Girls Chapter, 1998-1999 (Box 90, Folder 457)
  - Adolescent Health Book - Aricles & Background, 1998 (Box 90, Folder 458)
  - Adolescent Health Book - Contacts - 980207, 1997-1998 (Box 90, Folder 459)
  - Adolescent Health Book - Communication, 1999 (Box 90, Folder 460)
  - Adolescent Health Book - Information Sent to Authors, 1997-1998 (Box 90, Folder 461)
  - Adolescent Health Book - Sample Letter Sent Out to Perspective Author, 1998 (Box 90, Folder 462)
  - Adolescent Health Book - Tracking Sheet, 1999 (Box 91, Folder 463)
  - The Alpha Center for Health Planning - Contract - 990290, 1998-1999 (Box 91, Folder 464)
  - The Alpha Center for Health Planning - Proposal - Assessing the Effectiveness of the Commonwealth Fund's Communication and Dissemination Straregy and Products, 1998 Aug. 28 (Box 91, Folder 465)
  - The Alpha Center for Health Planning - Survey of Fund Audiences - Report to the Board of Directors, 1999 July 15 (Box 91, Folder 466)
  - American Enterprise Institute, 1992-1998 (Box 91, Folder 467)
  - American Enterprise Institute, 1992-1998 (Box 91, Folder 468)
  - American Enterprise Institute - 970315, 1996-1998 (Box 91, Folder 469)
  - The Anne E. Casey Foundation - 1999 Kids Count Data Book - State Profiles of Child Well-Being (Box 92, Folder 470)
  - Big Brothers/Big Sisters of NYC - 96674, 1996-1998 (Box 92, Folder 471)
  - Boston University - 96014 - Administration and Budget, 1995-1996 (Box 92, Folder 472)
  - Boston University - 96014 - Administration and Budget, 1996-1997 (Box 92, Folder 473)
  - Boston University - 96014 - Background Materials, 1995 (Box 92, Folder 474)
  - Boston University - 96014 - Carnegie Grant, 1996-1998 (Box 92, Folder 475)
  - Boston University - 96014 - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 92, Folder 476)
  - Boston University - 96014 - Correspondence, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 477)
  - Boston University - 96014 - Correspondence, 1996 March-May (Box 93, Folder 478)
  - Boston University - 96014, 1996 May-November (Box 93, Folder 479)
  - Boston University - 96014 - Denver Passport, 1992 (Box 93, Folder 480)
  - Boston University - 96014 - Expert Meetings, 1995 Sept., Dec. (Box 93, Folder 481)
  - Boston University - 96014 - Grant Products, 1996-1997 (Box 93, Folder 482)
  - Boston University - 96014 - Materials, Reviewers Comments, 1996 (Box 93, Folder 483)
  - Boston University - 96014 - Parent Group Meeting, 1995 (Box 93, Folder 484)
  - Boston University - 96014 - Parent Provider Review Sheets, 1996 (Box 93, Folder 485)
  - Boston University - 96014 - Parent Provider Review Sheets, 1996 (Box 94, Folder 486)
  - Boston University - 96014 - Parent Provider Review Sheets, 1996 (Box 94, Folder 487)
  - Boston University - 96014 - Parent Provider Review Sheets, 1996 (Box 94, Folder 488)
  - Boston University - 96014 - Provider Review Sheets - Mary Jo Ward, 1996 (Box 94, Folder 489)
  - Boston University - 96014 - Parent Provider Review Sheets, 1996-1997 (Box 94, Folder 490)
  - Boston University - 96014 - Parent Provider Review of Records, 1996-1997 (Box 95, Folder 491)
  - Boston University - 96014 - Phase One, 1995-1996 (Box 95, Folder 492)
  - Boston University - 96014 - Phase Two, 1995-1996 (Box 95, Folder 493)
  - Boston University - 96014 - Training Materials, 1995-1996 (Box 95, Folder 494)
  - Boston University - 96650 - Administration & Budget, 1996-1998 (Box 95, Folder 495)
  - Boston University - 96650 - Phase 2 - Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 96, Folder 496)
  - Boston University - 96650 - Phase 2 - Faxes, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 497)
  - Boston University - 96650 - Phase 2 - Grant Products, 1996-1997 (Box 96, Folder 498)
  - Boston University - 96650 - Phase 2 - Staff Training and Manual, 1996-1997 (Box 96, Folder 499)
  - Boston University - 96650 - Protocols, 1996 (Box 96, Folder 500)
  - Boston University - Training Institute - Zuckerman, 1996 July (Box 96, Folder 501)
  - Boston University - Training Institute - Zuckerman, 1996 November (Box 96, Folder 502)
  - Boston University - Training Institute - Zuckerman - Reviews, 1996 (Box 96, Folder 503)
  - Boston University - Training Institute - Training Meeting - Zuckerman, 1997 January 10 (Box 97, Folder 504)
  - Training Institute - Zuckerman/BU, 1997 March-April (Box 97, Folder 505)
  - Training Institute and Dinner - Zuckerman/BU, 1997 July 26 (Box 97, Folder 506)
  - Boston University - Training Grant - Phase 3, 1997-1999 (Box 97, Folder 507)
  - Boston University School of Medicine - Healthy Steps Planner, 1997 April 4-9 (Box 97, Folder 508)
  - Boston University School of Medicine - 980202 - Phase 4 - Administration, 1997-1998 (Box 97, Folder 509)
  - Boston University School of Medicine - 980202 - Phase 4 - Continuation of Funding Application, 1999 Dec. - 2000 Nov. 30 (Box 97, Folder 510)
  - Boston University School of Medicine - 980202 - Phase 4 - Correspondence/Notes, 1997-1998 (Box 97, Folder 511)
  - Boston University School of Medicine - 980202 - Phase 4 - Correspondence/Notes, 1998 (Box 98, Folder 512)
  - Boston University School of Medicine - 980202 - Phase 4 - Grant Products, 1997-1999 (Box 98, Folder 513)
  - Boston University School of Medicine - 980202 - Phase 4 - Grant Products, 1998-1999 (Box 98, Folder 514)
  - Boston University School of Medicine - 980202 - Phase 4 - Grant Products/Reports, 1997-1998 (Box 98, Folder 515)
  - Boston University School of Medicine - 980202 - Phase 4 - Progress Report, 1998 (Box 98, Folder 516)
  - Boston University School of Medicine - 980202 - Phase 4 - Proposal, P & R, LOA, 1997-1998 (Box 98, Frame 517)
  - Boston University School of Medicine - 980202 - Phase 4 - Technical Assistance - Conference Call Summaries, 1997 Sept. - Nov. (Box 98, Folder 518)
  - Boston University School of Medicine - 980202 - Phase 4 - Technical Assistance - E -Mail and To Do Lists, 1997-1998 (Box 99, Folder 519)
  - Boston University School of Medicine - 980202 - Phase 4 - Technical Assistance - E-Mails, 1998 (Box 99, Folder 520)
  - Boston University School of Medicine - 980202 - Phase 4 - Training Institute - Schedule - Zuckerman/BU, 1996-1998 (Box 99, Folder 521)
  - Boston University School of Medicine - 980202 - Phase 4 - Year II Training May - Zuckerman/BU, 1998 (Box 99, Folder 522)
  - Boston University School of Medicine - 980202 - Phase 4 - Year II Training March - Zuckerman/BU, 1998 (Box 99, Folder 523)
  - Boston University School of Medicine - 980202 - Phase 4 - Year II Training March, 1998 (Box 99, Folder 524)
  - Boston University - 990098 - Administration and Budget, 1998-2000 (Box 99, Folder 525)
  - Boston University - 990098 - Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 99, Folder 526)
  - Boston University - 990098 - Grant Products, 1998-1999 (Box 99, Folder 527)
  - Boston University - 990098 - Propposal, P &R, LOA, 1998-1999 (Box 99, Folder 528)
  - Boston University - 2000200 - Grant Products, 2000 March (Box 100, Folder 529)
  - Boston University - 2000200 - Grant Products, 2000-2001 (Box 100, Folder 530)
  - Boston University - 2000200 - Zuckerman, Barry S. M.D., 1999-2002 (Box 100, Folder 531)
  - Brandies University - New England Medical Center - 10170 - Administration and Budget, 1996-1997 (Box 100, Folder 532)
  - Brandies University - New England Medical Center - 10170 - Brandies Agreement/Mississippi, 1991-1993 (Box 100, Folder 533)
  - Brandies University - New England Medical Center - 10170 - Career Beginnings, 1994-1995, 1998 (Box 100, Folder 534)
  - Brandies University - New England Medical Center - 10170 - Correspondence, 1993-1997 (Box 100, Folder 535)
  - Brandies University - New England Medical Center - 10170 - Grant Products, 1994-1995 (Box 101, Folder 536)
  - Brandies University - New England Medical Center - 10170 - Grant Products, 1995-1996 (Box 101, Folder 537)
  - Brandies University - New England Medical Center - 10170 - Grant Products, 1996-1997 (Box 101, Folder 538)
  - Brandies University - New England Medical Center - 10170 - Main & School, 1995-1996 (Box 101, Folder 539)
  - UCLA - Background Materials - 970552, 1996-1997 (Box 101, Folder 540)
  - UCLA - Book Program - 970654, 1997-1998 (Box 101, Folder 541)
  - UCLA - Healthy Steps Survey Analysis 970654 - Administration, Budget. Proposal, 1997-1998 (Box 101, Folder 542)
  - UCLA - Healthy Steps Survey Analysis 970654 - Reports - Grant Products, 1997 (Box 101, Folder 543)
  - UCLA - Healthy Steps Survey Analysis 970654 - Grant Products - Chapters - 2nd Draft, 1998-2000 (Box 101, Folder 544-546)
  - Parent Survey - Maternal Risk Assessment - 960654, 1998 (Box 102, Folder 547)
  - Children's Hospital of Los Angeles - Parenting Assessment Tool 990229, 1998-2000 (Box 102, Folder 548)
  - Children Now - Children & Managed Care - 980136, 1997-1998 (Box 102, Folder 549)
  - Children Now - Key Notes and Background Info, 1997 July 1, December 16 (Box 102, Folder 550)
  - Children's Village - 96731, 1996-1998 (Box 102, Folder 551)
  - Coalitions of Community Foundations for Youth - Presentation at Summer Conference - 96770, 1996 (Box 102, Folder 552)
  - CASA at Columbia University - 970705, 1997-1999 (Box 102, Folder 553)
  - Committee for Economic Development - Employer Support for School - To - Work - 96739, 1996-1998 (Box 103, Folder 554)
  - Families and Work Institute - Kidsnet Video - The First Three Years, 1998 (Box 103, Folder 555)
  - Families and Work Institute - Kidsnet Video - The First Three Years, 1998 (Box 103, Folder 556)
  - Families and Work Institute - Kidsnet - 0123 - The First Three Years - A Guide to Selected Videos for Parents and Professionals, 1998 (Box 103, Folder 557)
  - Families and Work Institute - Administration & Budget - 95099, 1995-1998 (Box 103, Folder 558)
  - Families and Work Institute - Background Materials - 95099, 1996-1998 (Box 103, Folder 559)
  - Families and Work Institute - Correspondence - 95509, 1997-1998 (Box 104, Folder 560)
  - Families and Work Institute - Grant Product - 95099, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 561)
  - Families and Work Institute - Grant Product - 95099, 1997-1998 (Box 104, Folder 562)
  - Families and Work Institute - Grant Product - 95099, 1997-1998 (Box 104, Folder 563)
  - Families and Work Institute - Business Survey - 95475, 1995-1998 (Box 104, Folder 564)
  - Families and Work Institute - Employer Support for Expectant & New Parents - 96677, 1995-1996 (Box 104, Folder 565)
  - Families and Work Institute - Employer Support for Expectant & New Parents - 96677, 1997-1998 (Box 104, Folder 566)
  - Families and Work Institute - Video Review Meeting, 1996 Dec. 18 (Box 105, Folder 567)
  - Families and Work Institute - Video - 97058, 1996 (Box 105, Folder 568)
  - Families and Work Institute - Review and Parenting Materials Video - 97119, 1996-1997 (Box 105, Folder 569)
  - Families and Work Institute - Video Project - Kidsnet - 97119, 1997 (Box 105, Folder 570-572)
  - Families and Work Institute - Early Childhood Action Tips, 1998 (Box 106, Folder 573)
  - Families and Work Institute - The Early Childhood Public Engagement Campaign - Report to the Funders, 1998 April (Box 106, Folder 574-575)
  - Families and Work Institute - Measuring Progress and Results in Early Childhood System Development, 1998 (Box 106, Folder 576)
  - Grantmakers for Children, Youth, & Families, 1996-1998 (Box 106, Folder 577)
  - Grantmakers for Children, Youth & Families - Tides Foundation - 96649, 1995-1996 (Box 106, Folder 578)
  - Families and Work Institute - Year 2 Local Initiatives - Amarillo Area Foundation - 980238, 1998 (Box 106, Folder 579)
  - Families and Work Institute - Year 2 Local Initiatives - Blue Cross/Blue Shield of Kansas City - 980240, 1998 (Box 107, Folder 580)
  - Families and Work Institute - Year 2 Local Initiatives - Children's Hospital of Pittsburgh - 980239, 1997-1998 (Box 107, Folder 581)
  - Families and Work Institute - Year 2 Local Initiatives - Henry Ford Health System - 980241, 1997-1998 (Box 107, Folder 582)
  - Families and Work Institute - Year 2 Local Initiatives - New York Hospital - Cornell Medical Center - 980236, 1998 (Box 107, Folder 583)
  - Families and Work Institute - Status of Year 2 Grant Request From Funders to the CWF, 1998 (Box 107, Folder 584)
  - ICF - All Hands Meeting, 1997 July 9 (Box 107, Folder 585)
  - Board Meeting - ICF Incorporated - Concept Paper - Affiliate Sites, 1996-1997 (Box 107, Folder 586)
  - Board Meeting - ICF Incorporated - Program Director, 1997-1998 (Box 107, Folder 587)